# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.1
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = mixed positive
# senti_n = 3.826
# text = The meeting is open.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	meeting	meeting	NOUN	S1.1.3p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	open	open	ADJ	A10p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.2
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 3.446
# text = I would like to ask you to remain calm in the Chamber.
1	I	I	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Sing|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	would	would	AUX	A7p	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	like	like	VERB	E2p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
4	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	ask	ask	VERB	A5.4p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
6	you	you	PRON	A5.4p	Case=Acc|Person=2|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
7	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	remain	remain	VERB	T2p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
9	calm	calm	ADJ	E3p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
10	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
12	Chamber	Chamber	PROPN	H2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
13	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.3
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = mixed positive
# senti_n = 4.321
# text = We start with memoirs for Svend Jakobsen, and we particularly welcome Svend Jakobsen's family.
1	We	we	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Plur|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	start	start	VERB	T2p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=1|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	with	with	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	memoirs	memoir	NOUN	Q4.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
5	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
7	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER|SpaceAfter=No
8	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
9	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	we	we	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Plur|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
11	particularly	particularly	ADV	A13.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	welcome	welcome	VERB	Q2.2	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=1|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
13	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
14	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER|SpaceAfter=No
15	's	's	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	family	family	NOUN	S4	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
17	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.4
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 0.715
# text = It is with sorrow that the Danish Parliament has been informed that former Minister and Chairman of the Danish Parliament, Svend Aage Jakobsen (S), died on Saturday 28 May 2022.
1	It	it	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Neut|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	with	with	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	sorrow	sorrow	NOUN	E4.1n	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
5	that	that	SCONJ	A13.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
7	Danish	Danish	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
8	Parliament	Parliament	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
9	has	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
10	been	be	AUX	A3p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
11	informed	inform	VERB	X2.2p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
12	that	that	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	former	former	ADJ	T1.3	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
14	Minister	Minister	PROPN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
15	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	Chairman	Chairman	PROPN	S7.1p|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
17	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
18	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
19	Danish	Danish	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
20	Parliament	Parliament	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
21	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
22	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
23	Aage	Aage	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
24	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
25	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
26	S	S	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
27	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
28	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
29	died	die	VERB	L1n	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
30	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
31	Saturday	Saturday	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
32	28	28	NUM	Z2	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
33	May	May	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
34	2022	2022	NUM	Z2	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
35	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.5
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = mixed positive
# senti_n = 3.742
# text = Our thoughts and compassion go to Svend Jakobsen's family and close acquaintances.
1	Our	we	PRON	Z8	Number=Plur|Person=1|Poss=Yes|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	thoughts	thought	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
3	and	and	CCONJ	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	compassion	compassion	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
5	go	go	VERB	M1	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
6	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
8	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER|SpaceAfter=No
9	's	's	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	family	family	NOUN	S4	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
11	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	close	close	ADJ	N3.3n	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
13	acquaintances	acquaintance	NOUN	S3.1|S2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.6
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.305
# text = Svend Jakobsen was born on November 1, 1935 in a modest rural family in Vendsyssel.
1	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
2	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
3	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	born	bear	VERB	B1	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
5	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	November	November	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
7	1	1	NUM	Z2	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
8	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
9	1935	1935	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
10	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
12	modest	modest	ADJ	N3.2n	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
13	rural	rural	ADJ	F4|M7	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
14	family	family	NOUN	S4	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
15	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	Vendsyssel	Vendsyssel	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC|SpaceAfter=No
17	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.7
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = negative
# senti_n = 0.434
# text = He couldn't afford to go to real school, so he left school at the age of 14.
1	He	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	could	could	AUX	A7p	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
3	n't	not	PART	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	afford	afford	VERB	I1.1	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
5	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	go	go	VERB	M1	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
7	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	real	real	ADJ	A3p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
9	school	school	NOUN	P1|H1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
10	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	so	so	ADV	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
13	left	leave	VERB	M1	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
14	school	school	NOUN	P1|H1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
15	at	at	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
17	age	age	NOUN	T3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
18	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
19	14	14	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
20	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.8
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.664
# text = After working in agriculture for a few years he came to learn as a commission in the local farms.
1	After	after	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	working	work	VERB	I3.1	VerbForm=Ger	0	_	_	NER=O
3	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	agriculture	agriculture	NOUN	F4	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
5	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
7	few	few	ADJ	P1|S2	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
8	years	year	NOUN	P1|S2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
9	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
10	came	come	VERB	M1	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
11	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	learn	learn	VERB	X2.3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
13	as	as	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
14	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
15	commission	commission	NOUN	A1.1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
16	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
18	local	local	ADJ	M7	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
19	farms	farm	NOUN	F4|M7	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
20	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.9
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.604
# text = Already as a young man, Svend Jakobsen was interested in social relations, but it was while he worked at the head office of the FDB in Albertslund that he found his political position in the Social Democracy.
1	Already	already	ADV	T1.1.1	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	as	as	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
4	young	young	ADJ	T3n	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
5	man	man	NOUN	S2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
8	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
9	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
10	interested	interested	ADJ	X5.2p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
11	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	social	social	ADJ	S1.1.1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
13	relations	relation	NOUN	A2.2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
15	but	but	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	it	it	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Neut|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
17	was	be	VERB	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
18	while	while	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
19	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
20	worked	work	VERB	I3.1	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
21	at	at	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
22	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
23	head	head	NOUN	I2.1|H1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
24	office	office	NOUN	I2.1|H1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
25	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
27	FDB	FDB	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
28	in	in	ADP	Z2	_	0	_	_	NER=O
29	Albertslund	Albertslund	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC
30	that	that	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
31	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
32	found	find	VERB	A5.4p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
33	his	he	PRON	A5.4p	Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|Poss=Yes|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
34	political	political	ADJ	G1.2	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
35	position	position	NOUN	M6	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
36	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
37	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
38	Social	social	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
39	Democracy	Democracy	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
40	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.10
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.968
# text = As far back as 1971 Svend Jakobsen was elected to the Folketing for the first time.
1	As	as	ADV	A13	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	far	far	ADV	A13.3	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
3	back	back	ADV	M6	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	as	as	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	1971	1971	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
6	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
7	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
8	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
9	elected	elect	VERB	G1.2|X7p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
10	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
12	Folketing	Folketing	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
13	for	for	ADP	N4	_	0	_	_	NER=O
14	the	the	DET	N4	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
15	first	first	ADJ	N4	Degree=Pos|NumType=Ord	0	_	_	NER=O
16	time	time	NOUN	N4	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
17	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.11
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.704
# text = Two years later he became a short-term minister of housing in Anker Jørgensen's first ministry.
1	Two	two	NUM	N1	NumForm=Word|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
2	years	year	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
3	later	late	ADV	T4n	Degree=Cmp	0	_	_	NER=O
4	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
5	became	become	VERB	A2.1p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
6	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
7	short	short	ADJ	T1.3n	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
8	-	-	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
9	term	term	NOUN	Q3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
10	minister	minister	NOUN	G1.1|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
11	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	housing	housing	NOUN	H1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
13	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
14	Anker	Anker	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
15	Jørgensen	Jørgensen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
16	's	's	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	first	first	ADJ	N4	Degree=Pos|NumType=Ord	0	_	_	NER=O
18	ministry	ministry	NOUN	G1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.12
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.427
# text = From 1973 to 1981 he held various ministerial posts, and every time Anker Jørgensen formed a new government, Svend Jakobsen was invited for tasks with ever greater responsibility.
1	From	from	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	1973	1973	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
3	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	1981	1981	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
5	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
6	held	hold	VERB	M2	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
7	various	various	ADJ	A6.3p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
8	ministerial	ministerial	ADJ	G1.1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
9	posts	post	NOUN	Q1.2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
10	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	every	every	DET	N5.1p	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	time	time	NOUN	T1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
14	Anker	Anker	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
15	Jørgensen	Jørgensen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
16	formed	form	VERB	T2p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
17	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
18	new	new	ADJ	T3n	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
19	government	government	NOUN	G1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
20	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
21	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
22	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
23	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
24	invited	invite	VERB	Q2.2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
25	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	tasks	task	NOUN	A1.1.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
27	with	with	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	ever	ever	ADV	T1.1	_	0	_	_	NER=O
29	greater	great	ADJ	A5.1p	Degree=Cmp	0	_	_	NER=O
30	responsibility	responsibility	NOUN	S6p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
31	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.13
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = positive
# senti_n = 5.405
# text = He was pragmatic and reliable, and he knew his material.
1	He	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	pragmatic	pragmatic	ADJ	Q3	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
4	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	reliable	reliable	ADJ	A5.1p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
9	knew	know	VERB	A5.4p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
10	his	he	PRON	A5.4p	Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|Poss=Yes|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
11	material	material	NOUN	O1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
12	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.14
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.883
# text = In addition to the Minister for Housing, Svend Jakobsen managed to be Minister for Taxation, Fisheries and Finance.
1	In	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	addition	addition	NOUN	N5p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
5	Minister	Minister	PROPN	G1.1|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
6	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	Housing	Housing	PROPN	H1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
8	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
9	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
10	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
11	managed	manage	VERB	S7.1p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
12	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
14	Minister	minister	NOUN	G1.1|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
15	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	Taxation	Taxation	PROPN	I1.1|G1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
17	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
18	Fisheries	Fishery	PROPN	F4|M4	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
19	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
20	Finance	Finance	PROPN	I1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
21	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.15
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 3.367
# text = The trusted tasks were solved without anyone being able to put a finger on his work.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	trusted	trust	VERB	X2.1	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
3	tasks	task	NOUN	A1.1.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
4	were	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
5	solved	solve	VERB	X9.2p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
6	without	without	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	anyone	anyone	PRON	Z8	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
8	being	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Ger	0	_	_	NER=O
9	able	able	ADJ	X9.1p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
10	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	put	put	VERB	X2.2p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
12	a	a	DET	X2.2p	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
13	finger	finger	NOUN	X2.2p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
14	on	on	ADP	X2.2p	_	0	_	_	NER=O
15	his	he	PRON	Z8	Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|Poss=Yes|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
16	work	work	NOUN	I3.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
17	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.16
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = positive
# senti_n = 4.625
# text = And then Svend Jakobsen was known for an eminent memory.
1	And	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	then	then	ADV	N4	PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
3	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
4	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
5	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
6	known	know	VERB	X2.2p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
7	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	an	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
9	eminent	eminent	ADJ	X9.1p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
10	memory	memory	NOUN	X2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
11	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.17
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 3.261
# text = On 22 December 1981 he was elected President of the Folketing.
1	On	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	22	22	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
3	December	December	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	1981	1981	NUM	Z2	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
5	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
6	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
7	elected	elect	VERB	G1.2|X7p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
8	President	President	PROPN	G1.1|S7.1p|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
9	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
11	Folketing	Folketing	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
12	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.18
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = positive
# senti_n = 4.538
# text = On that occasion he called the day the happiest day of my life as a politician.
1	On	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	that	that	DET	Z5	Number=Sing|PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
3	occasion	occasion	NOUN	T1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
5	called	call	VERB	Q2.2	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
6	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
7	day	day	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
8	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
9	happiest	happy	ADJ	E4.1p	Degree=Sup	0	_	_	NER=O
10	day	day	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
11	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	my	my	PRON	Z8	Number=Sing|Person=1|Poss=Yes|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
13	life	life	NOUN	L1p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
14	as	as	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
15	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
16	politician	politician	NOUN	G1.2|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
17	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.19
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.695
# text = Until 1989 he was responsible, as President of Parliament, for the legislative work to be carried out as described in the Constitution and in the Rules of Procedure of the Danish Parliament.
1	Until	until	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	1989	1989	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
3	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
4	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
5	responsible	responsible	ADJ	A2.2	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	as	as	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	President	President	PROPN	G1.1|S7.1p|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
9	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	Parliament	Parliament	PROPN	G1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
11	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
14	legislative	legislative	ADJ	G2.1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
15	work	work	NOUN	I3.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
16	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
18	carried	carry	VERB	M2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
19	out	out	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
20	as	as	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
21	described	describe	VERB	Q2.2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
22	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
23	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
24	Constitution	Constitution	PROPN	G1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
25	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
27	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
28	Rules	rule	PROPN	G2.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
29	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
30	Procedure	Procedure	PROPN	X4.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
31	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
32	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
33	Danish	Danish	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
34	Parliament	Parliament	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
35	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.20
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 1.038
# text = But it must be said that it has not been without challenges.
1	But	but	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	it	it	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Neut|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
3	must	must	AUX	S6p	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
5	said	say	VERB	Q2.1	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
6	that	that	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	it	it	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Neut|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
8	has	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
9	not	not	PART	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	been	be	AUX	A3p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
11	without	without	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	challenges	challenge	NOUN	A12n	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
13	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.21
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 0.518
# text = It was during those years when Mogen Glistrup and Preben Møller Hansen were known for very bram-free statements that often broke with tact and tone in the Assembly Hall.
1	It	it	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Neut|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	during	during	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	those	that	DET	Z5	Number=Plur|PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
5	years	year	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
6	when	when	SCONJ	Z5	PronType=Int	0	_	_	NER=O
7	Mogen	Mogen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
8	Glistrup	Glistrup	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
9	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	Preben	Preben	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
11	Møller	Møller	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
12	Hansen	Hansen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
13	were	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
14	known	know	VERB	X2.2p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
15	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	very	very	ADV	A13.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	bram	bram	NOUN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
18	-	-	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	free	free	ADJ	S6n	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
20	statements	statement	NOUN	Q2.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
21	that	that	PRON	A13.3	PronType=Rel	0	_	_	NER=O
22	often	often	ADV	N6p	_	0	_	_	NER=O
23	broke	break	VERB	A1.1.2	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
24	with	with	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
25	tact	tact	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
26	and	and	CCONJ	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
27	tone	tone	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
28	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
29	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
30	Assembly	Assembly	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC
31	Hall	Hall	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-LOC|SpaceAfter=No
32	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.22
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = mixed positive
# senti_n = 4.407
# text = I think everyone agreed that Svend Jakobsen handled the episodes of the unruly language from the platform with a mixture of authority and sense of situation.
1	I	I	PRON	Z4	Case=Nom|Number=Sing|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	think	think	VERB	Z4	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=1|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	everyone	everyone	PRON	Z8|N5.1p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	agreed	agree	VERB	A6.1p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
5	that	that	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
7	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
8	handled	handle	VERB	A1.1.1	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
9	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
10	episodes	episode	NOUN	A3p|A11.1p	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
11	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
13	unruly	unruly	ADJ	A1.7n	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
14	language	language	NOUN	Q3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
15	from	from	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
17	platform	platform	NOUN	M3|M7	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
18	with	with	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
19	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
20	mixture	mixture	NOUN	O1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
21	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
22	authority	authority	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
23	and	and	CCONJ	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
24	sense	sense	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
25	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	situation	situation	NOUN	A3p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
27	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.23
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.743
# text = Svend Jakobsen left active policy in 1989 first to become director of the Danish savings fund association and after a merger managing director of the Finance Council from 1990 to 1994.
1	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
2	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
3	left	leave	VERB	M1	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	active	active	ADJ	X5.2p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
5	policy	policy	NOUN	X7p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
6	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	1989	1989	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
8	first	first	ADV	N4	Degree=Pos|NumType=Ord	0	_	_	NER=O
9	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	become	become	VERB	A2.1p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
11	director	director	NOUN	S7.1p|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
12	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
14	Danish	Danish	ADJ	Z2	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
15	savings	savings	NOUN	I1.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
16	fund	fund	NOUN	I1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
17	association	association	NOUN	S5p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
18	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
19	after	after	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
20	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
21	merger	merger	NOUN	S5p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
22	managing	manage	NOUN	S7.1p|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
23	director	director	NOUN	S7.1p|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
24	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
25	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
26	Finance	Finance	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
27	Council	Council	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
28	from	from	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
29	1990	1990	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
30	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
31	1994	1994	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
32	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.24
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = mixed positive
# senti_n = 3.834
# text = For Svend Jakobsen it was always the case that was at the centre.
1	For	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
3	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
4	it	it	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Neut|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
5	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
6	always	always	ADV	N6p	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
8	case	case	NOUN	A4.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
9	that	that	PRON	A13.3	PronType=Rel	0	_	_	NER=O
10	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
11	at	at	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
13	centre	centre	NOUN	M6	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.25
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 0.759
# text = He had a very quiet background, he let the results speak for himself and would like to underplay his own meaning in order to achieve the final result.
1	He	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	had	have	VERB	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
4	very	very	ADV	A13.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	quiet	quiet	ADJ	X3.2n	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
6	background	background	NOUN	T1.1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
9	let	let	VERB	S7.4p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
10	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
11	results	result	NOUN	A2.2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
12	speak	speak	VERB	Q2.1	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
13	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
14	himself	himself	PRON	Z8	Case=Acc|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs|Reflex=Yes	0	_	_	NER=O
15	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	would	would	AUX	A7p	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
17	like	like	VERB	E2p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
18	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
19	underplay	underplay	VERB	A5.4p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
20	his	he	PRON	A5.4p	Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|Poss=Yes|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
21	own	own	ADJ	A9p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
22	meaning	meaning	NOUN	X2.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
23	in	in	SCONJ	A5.3p	_	0	_	_	NER=O
24	order	order	NOUN	A5.3p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
25	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	achieve	achieve	VERB	A9p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
27	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
28	final	final	ADJ	N4	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
29	result	result	NOUN	A2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
30	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.26
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.715
# text = When he was 75 years old, a reporter asked if there was no book of memoirs coming.
1	When	when	SCONJ	Z5	PronType=Int	0	_	_	NER=O
2	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
3	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	75	75	NUM	T3	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
5	years	year	NOUN	T3	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
6	old	old	ADJ	T3	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
9	reporter	reporter	NOUN	Q4.2|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
10	asked	ask	VERB	Q2.2	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
11	if	if	SCONJ	Z7	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	there	there	PRON	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	was	be	VERB	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
14	no	no	DET	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=O
15	book	book	NOUN	Q4.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
16	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	memoirs	memoir	NOUN	Q4.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
18	coming	come	VERB	M1	VerbForm=Ger	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.27
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = negative
# senti_n = 0.153
# text = It was clearly rejected with a crunchy remark that several other biographies are characterized by a self-promotion that does not correspond to what I know of the individual's performance.
1	It	it	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Neut|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	was	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	clearly	clearly	ADV	A7p	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	rejected	reject	VERB	X7n	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
5	with	with	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
7	crunchy	crunchy	ADJ	O4.5	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
8	remark	remark	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
9	that	that	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	several	several	ADJ	N5	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
11	other	other	ADJ	A6.1n	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
12	biographies	biography	NOUN	Q4.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
13	are	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
14	characterized	characterize	VERB	A4.1	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
15	by	by	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	a	a	DET	Z8	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
17	self	self	NOUN	Z8	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
18	-	-	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	promotion	promotion	NOUN	S7.1p|A2.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
20	that	that	PRON	A13.3	PronType=Rel	0	_	_	NER=O
21	does	do	AUX	A1.1.1	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
22	not	not	PART	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=O
23	correspond	correspond	VERB	Q1.2	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
24	to	to	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
25	what	what	PRON	Z8	PronType=Int	0	_	_	NER=O
26	I	I	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Sing|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
27	know	know	VERB	X2.2p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=1|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
28	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
29	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
30	individual	individual	NOUN	S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
31	's	's	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
32	performance	performance	NOUN	K4	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
33	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.28
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = mixed positive
# senti_n = 4.310
# text = ▪ And perhaps the note contains the key to understanding the virtues on which Svend Jakobsen built his political action: secularity, thoroughness, modesty, thoughtfulness, and not least diligence.
1	▪	▪	PUNCT	Z99	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	And	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	perhaps	perhaps	ADV	A7	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
5	note	note	NOUN	Q1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
6	contains	contain	VERB	A1.8p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
7	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
8	key	key	NOUN	O2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
9	to	to	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	understanding	understand	VERB	X2.5p	VerbForm=Ger	0	_	_	NER=O
11	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
12	virtues	virtue	NOUN	G2.2p	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
13	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
14	which	which	PRON	Z5	PronType=Rel	0	_	_	NER=O
15	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
16	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
17	built	build	VERB	A5.4p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
18	his	he	PRON	A5.4p	Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|Poss=Yes|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
19	political	political	ADJ	G1.2	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
20	action	action	NOUN	A1.1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
21	:	:	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
22	secularity	secularity	NOUN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
23	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
24	thoroughness	thoroughness	NOUN	N5.1p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
25	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	modesty	modesty	NOUN	S1.2.3n	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
27	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	thoughtfulness	thoughtfulness	NOUN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
29	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
30	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
31	not	not	PART	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=O
32	least	least	ADJ	N5.1n	Degree=Sup	0	_	_	NER=O
33	diligence	diligence	NOUN	X5.2p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
34	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.29
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = positive
# senti_n = 4.649
# text = The same qualities made Svend Jakobsen widely respected among both political friends and opponents.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	same	same	ADJ	A6.1p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
3	qualities	quality	NOUN	A5.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
4	made	make	VERB	A1.1.1	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
5	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
6	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
7	widely	widely	ADV	N5p	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	respected	respect	VERB	S7.2p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
9	among	among	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	both	both	CCONJ	N5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	political	political	ADJ	G1.2	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
12	friends	friend	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
13	and	and	CCONJ	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
14	opponents	opponent	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
15	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.30
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = mixed positive
# senti_n = 3.963
# text = I ask you to rise up so that we may honor Svend Jakobsen's memory.
1	I	I	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Sing|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	ask	ask	VERB	A5.4p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=1|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	you	you	PRON	A5.4p	Case=Acc|Person=2|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
4	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	rise	rise	VERB	M1	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
6	up	up	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	so	so	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	that	that	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
9	we	we	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Plur|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
10	may	may	AUX	A7p	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
11	honor	honor	VERB	Z99	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
12	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
13	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER|SpaceAfter=No
14	's	's	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
15	memory	memory	NOUN	X2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
16	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101501.seg1.31
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = positive
# senti_n = 4.725
# text = Glory be to Svend Jakobsen's memory!
1	Glory	glory	NOUN	S7.2p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
2	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	Svend	Svend	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
5	Jakobsen	Jakobsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER|SpaceAfter=No
6	's	's	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	memory	memory	NOUN	X2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
8	!	!	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.1
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = mixed positive
# senti_n = 3.630
# text = Then we move on to today's assignments.
1	Then	then	ADV	N4	PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
2	we	we	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Plur|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
3	move	move	VERB	M2	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=1|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	today	today	NOUN	T1.1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	's	's	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	assignments	assignment	NOUN	P1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
9	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.2
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 1.910
# text = The Minister for Business (Simon Kollerup) has informed me that he wishes to withdraw the following proposals: Proposal for a law on the regulation of social media.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	Minister	Minister	PROPN	G1.1|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	Business	Business	PROPN	I2.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
5	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	Simon	Simon	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
7	Kollerup	Kollerup	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER|SpaceAfter=No
8	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
9	has	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
10	informed	inform	VERB	A5.4p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
11	me	I	PRON	A5.4p	Case=Acc|Number=Sing|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
12	that	that	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	he	he	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Masc|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
14	wishes	wish	VERB	X7p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
15	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	withdraw	withdraw	VERB	M2	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
17	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
18	following	follow	VERB	M1	VerbForm=Ger	0	_	_	NER=O
19	proposals	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
20	:	:	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
21	Proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
22	for	for	ADP	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
23	a	a	DET	T1.3	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
24	law	law	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
25	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
27	regulation	regulation	NOUN	G2.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
28	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
29	social	social	ADJ	S1.1.1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
30	media	media	NOUN	Q4	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
31	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.3
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 3.103
# text = L 146).
1	L	l	SYM	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	146	146	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
3	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
4	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.4
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.868
# text = Does anyone wish to include this bill?
1	Does	do	AUX	S1.1.3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
2	anyone	anyone	PRON	Z8	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	wish	wish	VERB	X7p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
4	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	include	include	VERB	A1.8p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
6	this	this	DET	M6	Number=Sing|PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
7	bill	bill	NOUN	I1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
8	?	?	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.5
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 1.554
# text = As this is not the case, the draft law has lapsed.
1	As	as	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	this	this	PRON	M6	Number=Sing|PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
3	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	not	not	PART	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
6	case	case	NOUN	A4.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
9	draft	draft	NOUN	Q1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
10	law	law	NOUN	G2.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
11	has	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
12	lapsed	lap	VERB	B1|L2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
13	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.6
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 1.116
# text = Members of the Folketing Pernille Skipper (EL) and others I have been informed that they wish to withdraw the following proposals: the motion for a resolution on the parliamentary vote to reject Polish abortion legislation unequivocally.
1	Members	member	NOUN	S5p|S2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
2	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
4	Folketing	Folketing	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
5	Pernille	Pernille	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
6	Skipper	Skipper	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
7	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
8	EL	EL	PROPN	M5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
9	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	others	other	NOUN	A6.1n|Z8	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
12	I	I	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Sing|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
13	have	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=1|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
14	been	be	AUX	A3p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
15	informed	inform	VERB	X2.2p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
16	that	that	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	they	they	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Plur|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
18	wish	wish	VERB	X7p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
19	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
20	withdraw	withdraw	VERB	M2	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
21	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
22	following	follow	VERB	M1	VerbForm=Ger	0	_	_	NER=O
23	proposals	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
24	:	:	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
25	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
26	motion	motion	NOUN	M1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
27	for	for	ADP	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	a	a	DET	T1.3	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
29	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
30	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
31	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
32	parliamentary	parliamentary	ADJ	G1.1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
33	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
34	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
35	reject	reject	VERB	X7n	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
36	Polish	Polish	ADJ	Z2	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
37	abortion	abortion	NOUN	B3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
38	legislation	legislation	NOUN	G2.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
39	unequivocally	unequivocally	ADV	A7p	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
40	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.7
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 3.064
# text = B100.
1	B100	B100	NUM	Z99	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
2	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.8
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.926
# text = Does anyone wish to include this motion for a resolution?
1	Does	do	AUX	S1.1.3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
2	anyone	anyone	PRON	Z8	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	wish	wish	VERB	X7p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
4	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	include	include	VERB	A1.8p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
6	this	this	DET	M6	Number=Sing|PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
7	motion	motion	NOUN	M1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
8	for	for	ADP	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
9	a	a	DET	T1.3	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
10	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
11	?	?	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.9
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 1.594
# text = As this is not the case, the motion for a resolution has lapsed.
1	As	as	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	this	this	PRON	M6	Number=Sing|PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
3	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	not	not	PART	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
6	case	case	NOUN	A4.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
9	motion	motion	NOUN	M1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
10	for	for	ADP	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	a	a	DET	T1.3	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
12	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
13	has	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
14	lapsed	lap	VERB	B1|L2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
15	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.10
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 1.206
# text = Members of the Danish Parliament Charlotte Broman Mølbæk (SF) and Trine Torp (SF) have informed me that they want to take back questions to the Minister for Social Affairs and the elderly and the Minister for Education about children in vulnerable positions in daily offers.
1	Members	member	NOUN	S5p|S2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
2	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
4	Danish	Danish	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
5	Parliament	Parliament	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
6	Charlotte	Charlotte	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
7	Broman	Broman	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
8	Mølbæk	Mølbæk	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
9	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
10	SF	SF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
11	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	Trine	Trine	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
14	Torp	Torp	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
15	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
16	SF	SF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
17	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
18	have	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
19	informed	inform	VERB	A5.4p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
20	me	I	PRON	A5.4p	Case=Acc|Number=Sing|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
21	that	that	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
22	they	they	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Plur|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
23	want	want	VERB	X7p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
24	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
25	take	take	VERB	A9p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
26	back	back	ADV	B1	_	0	_	_	NER=O
27	questions	question	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
28	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
29	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
30	Minister	Minister	PROPN	G1.1|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
31	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
32	Social	social	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
33	Affairs	affair	PROPN	Z1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
34	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
35	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
36	elderly	elderly	NOUN	T3p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
37	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
38	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
39	Minister	Minister	PROPN	G1.1|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
40	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
41	Education	Education	PROPN	P1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
42	about	about	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
43	children	child	NOUN	S2|T3n	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
44	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
45	vulnerable	vulnerable	ADJ	S1.2.5n	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
46	positions	position	NOUN	M6	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
47	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
48	daily	daily	ADJ	T1.1.2	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
49	offers	offer	NOUN	A9n	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
50	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.11
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 3.141
# text = F 40).
1	F	F	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
2	40	40	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
3	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
4	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.12
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.380
# text = The question has now been dropped.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	question	question	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	has	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	now	now	ADV	T1.1.2	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	been	be	AUX	A3p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
6	dropped	drop	VERB	M2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.13
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 1.264
# text = Members of the Danish Parliament Morten Messerschmidt (DF) and René Christensen (DF) have informed me that they want to take back questions to the Minister for Climate, Energy and Supply about the energy crisis and the green transition.
1	Members	member	NOUN	S5p|S2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
2	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
4	Danish	Danish	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
5	Parliament	Parliament	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
6	Morten	Morten	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
7	Messerschmidt	Messerschmidt	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
8	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
9	DF	DF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
10	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	René	René	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
13	Christensen	Christensen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
14	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
15	DF	DF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
16	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	have	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
18	informed	inform	VERB	A5.4p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
19	me	I	PRON	A5.4p	Case=Acc|Number=Sing|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
20	that	that	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
21	they	they	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Plur|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
22	want	want	VERB	X7p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
23	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
24	take	take	VERB	A9p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
25	back	back	ADV	B1	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	questions	question	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
27	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
29	Minister	minister	NOUN	G1.1|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
30	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
31	Climate	Climate	PROPN	W4	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
32	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
33	Energy	Energy	PROPN	X5.2p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
34	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
35	Supply	Supply	PROPN	A9n	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
36	about	about	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
37	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
38	energy	energy	NOUN	X5.2p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
39	crisis	crisis	NOUN	A12n	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
40	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
41	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
42	green	green	ADJ	O4.3	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
43	transition	transition	NOUN	A2.1p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
44	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.14
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 3.164
# text = F 45).
1	F	F	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
2	45	45	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
3	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
4	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602101959.seg2.15
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 1.877
# text = The question entered as item 31 of the agenda has now been dropped and deleted from the agenda.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	question	question	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	entered	enter	VERB	M1	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	as	as	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	item	item	NOUN	O2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
6	31	31	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
7	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
9	agenda	agenda	NOUN	Q1.2|X7p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
10	has	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
11	now	now	ADV	T1.1.2	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	been	be	AUX	A3p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
13	dropped	drop	VERB	M2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
14	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
15	deleted	delete	VERB	Q1.2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
16	from	from	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
18	agenda	agenda	NOUN	Q1.2|X7p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102106
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102106.seg3
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102106.seg3.1
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.134
# text = The item listed as No. 3 on the agenda, can only be dealt with in this sitting with the agreement of the House.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	item	item	NOUN	O2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	listed	list	VERB	Q1.2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
4	as	as	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	No.	no.	NOUN	Z99	Abbr=Yes|Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
6	3	3	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
7	on	on	ADP	A7p	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	the	the	DET	A7p	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
9	agenda	agenda	NOUN	A7p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
10	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	can	can	AUX	A7p	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
12	only	only	ADV	A14	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
14	dealt	deal	VERB	A1.1.1	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
15	with	with	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	this	this	DET	M6	Number=Sing|PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
18	sitting	sitting	NOUN	M8	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
19	with	with	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
20	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
21	agreement	agreement	NOUN	A6.1p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
22	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
23	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
24	House	House	PROPN	H4	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
25	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102106.seg3.2
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.867
# text = And if no one objects, I consider the consent given.
1	And	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	if	if	SCONJ	Z7	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	no	no	DET	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	one	one	NOUN	N1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
5	objects	object	VERB	A6.1n	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	I	I	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Sing|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
8	consider	consider	VERB	X2.1	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=1|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
9	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
10	consent	consent	NOUN	S7.4p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
11	given	give	VERB	A9n	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
12	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102106.seg3.3
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = mixed positive
# senti_n = 4.154
# text = It's a matter of course.
1	It	it	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Gender=Neut|Number=Sing|Person=3|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
2	's	be	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
4	matter	matter	NOUN	X4.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
5	of	of	ADP	Z5	ExtPos=ADV	0	_	_	NER=O
6	course	course	NOUN	M6	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.1
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.913
# text = The debate is closed and we shall proceed to the vote on the proposed amendments for adoption.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	debate	debate	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	closed	close	VERB	A1.1.1	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
5	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	we	we	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Plur|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
7	shall	shall	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
8	proceed	proceed	VERB	A1.1.1	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
9	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
11	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
12	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
14	proposed	propose	VERB	Q2.2|X7p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
15	amendments	amendment	NOUN	A2.1p	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
16	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	adoption	adoption	NOUN	A9p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
18	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.2
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 3.347
# text = There are four proposals.
1	There	there	PRON	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	are	be	VERB	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	four	four	NUM	N1	NumForm=Word|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
4	proposals	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.3
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.531
# text = The vote shall be taken first on the motion for a resolution No. V 88 by Rasmus Horn Langhoff (S) and Kirsten Normann Andersen (SF), and voting is possible.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	shall	shall	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
5	taken	take	VERB	A9p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
6	first	first	ADV	N4	NumType=Ord	0	_	_	NER=O
7	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
9	motion	motion	NOUN	M1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
10	for	for	ADP	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	a	a	DET	T1.3	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
12	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
13	No.	no.	NOUN	Z2	Abbr=Yes|Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
14	V	V	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
15	88	88	NUM	Z2	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
16	by	by	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	Rasmus	Rasmus	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
18	Horn	Horn	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
19	Langhoff	Langhoff	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
20	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
21	S	S	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
22	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
23	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
24	Kirsten	Kirsten	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
25	Normann	Normann	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
26	Andersen	Andersen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
27	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
28	SF	SF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
29	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
30	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
31	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
32	voting	voting	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
33	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
34	possible	possible	ADJ	A7p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
35	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.4
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.751
# text = The vote will end.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	will	will	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	end	end	VERB	T2n	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.5
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 1.461
# text = In favour of 36 (S and SF), against 59 (V, RV, EL, KF, DF, NB, LA, FG, ALT, Bent Bøgsted (UFG), Lise Bech (UFG) and Marie Krarup (UFG)), abstentions 0.
1	In	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	favour	favour	NOUN	S8p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	36	36	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
5	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	S	S	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
7	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	SF	SF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
9	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
10	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	against	against	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	59	59	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
13	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
15	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	RV	RV	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
17	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
18	EL	EL	PROPN	M5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
20	KF	KF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
21	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
22	DF	DF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
23	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
24	NB	NB	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
25	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	LA	LA	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC|SpaceAfter=No
27	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	FG	FG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
29	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
30	ALT	ALT	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
31	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
32	Bent	Bent	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
33	Bøgsted	Bøgsted	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
34	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
35	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
36	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
37	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
38	Lise	Lise	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
39	Bech	Bech	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
40	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
41	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
42	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
43	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
44	Marie	Marie	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
45	Krarup	Krarup	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
46	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
47	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
48	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
49	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
50	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
51	abstentions	abstention	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
52	0	0	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
53	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.6
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 1.459
# text = Proposal for adoption No The V 88 is rejected.
1	Proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
2	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	adoption	adoption	NOUN	A9p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	No	no	DET	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
5	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
6	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
7	88	88	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
8	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
9	rejected	reject	VERB	X7n	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
10	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.7
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.424
# text = The vote shall then be taken on the proposal for adoption No. V 87 by Liselott Blixt (UFG), Martin Geertsen (V), Per Larsen (KF), Jens Henrik Thulesen Dahl (DF), Susanne Zimmer (FG), Karina Adsbøl (UFG), Lise Bech (UFG), Bent Bøgsted (UFG), Marie Krarup (UFG) and Hans Kristian Skibby (UFG), and voting is possible.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	shall	shall	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	then	then	ADV	N4	PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
5	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
6	taken	take	VERB	A9p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
7	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
9	proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
10	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	adoption	adoption	NOUN	A9p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
12	No.	no.	NOUN	Z2	Abbr=Yes|Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
13	V	V	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
14	87	87	NUM	Z2	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
15	by	by	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	Liselott	Liselott	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
17	Blixt	Blixt	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
18	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
20	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
21	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
22	Martin	Martin	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
23	Geertsen	Geertsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
24	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
25	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
26	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
27	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	Per	Per	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
29	Larsen	Larsen	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
30	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
31	KF	KF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
32	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
33	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
34	Jens	Jens	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
35	Henrik	Henrik	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
36	Thulesen	Thulesen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
37	Dahl	Dahl	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
38	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
39	DF	DF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
40	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
41	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
42	Susanne	Susanne	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
43	Zimmer	Zimmer	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
44	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
45	FG	FG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
46	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
47	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
48	Karina	Karina	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
49	Adsbøl	Adsbøl	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
50	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
51	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
52	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
53	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
54	Lise	Lise	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
55	Bech	Bech	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
56	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
57	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
58	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
59	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
60	Bent	Bent	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
61	Bøgsted	Bøgsted	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
62	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
63	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
64	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
65	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
66	Marie	Marie	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
67	Krarup	Krarup	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
68	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
69	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
70	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
71	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
72	Hans	Hans	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
73	Kristian	Kristian	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
74	Skibby	Skibby	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
75	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
76	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
77	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
78	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
79	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
80	voting	voting	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
81	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
82	possible	possible	ADJ	A7p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
83	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.8
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.751
# text = The vote will end.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	will	will	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	end	end	VERB	T2n	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.9
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 1.765
# text = For the vote 42 (V, KF, DF, NB, FG, Bent Bøgsted (UFG), Lise Bech (UFG) and Marie Krarup (UFG)), against 56 (S, SF, RV, EL, LA and ALT), abstentions 0.
1	For	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
3	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	42	42	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
5	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	KF	KF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
9	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	DF	DF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
11	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	NB	NB	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
13	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
14	FG	FG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
15	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	Bent	Bent	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
17	Bøgsted	Bøgsted	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
18	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
20	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
21	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
22	Lise	Lise	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
23	Bech	Bech	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
24	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
25	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
26	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
27	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	Marie	Marie	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
29	Krarup	Krarup	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
30	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
31	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
32	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
33	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
34	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
35	against	against	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
36	56	56	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
37	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
38	S	S	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
39	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
40	SF	SF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
41	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
42	RV	RV	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
43	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
44	EL	EL	PROPN	M5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC|SpaceAfter=No
45	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
46	LA	LA	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
47	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
48	ALT	ALT	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
49	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
50	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
51	abstentions	abstention	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
52	0	0	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
53	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.10
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 1.450
# text = Proposal for adoption No V 87 is rejected.
1	Proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
2	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	adoption	adoption	NOUN	A9p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	No	no	DET	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
5	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
6	87	87	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
7	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
8	rejected	reject	VERB	X7n	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
9	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.11
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.596
# text = The vote will then be taken on the motion for a resolution (Doc. V 89 by Stinus Lindgreen (RV) and Henrik Dahl (LA), and voting is possible.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	will	will	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	then	then	ADV	N4	PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
5	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
6	taken	take	VERB	A9p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
7	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
9	motion	motion	NOUN	M1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
10	for	for	ADP	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	a	a	DET	T1.3	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
12	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
13	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	Doc.	Doc.	PROPN	T1.3	Abbr=Yes|Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
15	V	V	PROPN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
16	89	89	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
17	by	by	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
18	Stinus	Stinus	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
19	Lindgreen	Lindgreen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
20	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
21	RV	RV	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
22	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
23	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
24	Henrik	Henrik	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
25	Dahl	Dahl	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
26	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
27	LA	LA	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC|SpaceAfter=No
28	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
29	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
30	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
31	voting	voting	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
32	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
33	possible	possible	ADJ	A7p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
34	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.12
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.751
# text = The vote will end.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	will	will	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	end	end	VERB	T2n	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.13
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 1.497
# text = In favour of voting 11 (RV and LA), against voting 85 (S, V, SF, EL, KF, DF, NB, FG, ALT, Bent Bøgsted (UFG), Lise Bech (UFG) and Marie Krarup (UFG), abstention 0.
1	In	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	favour	favour	NOUN	S8p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	of	of	SCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	voting	voting	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
5	11	11	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
6	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	RV	RV	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
8	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
9	LA	LA	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
10	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
11	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	against	against	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	voting	voting	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
14	85	85	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
15	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
16	S	S	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
17	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
18	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
20	SF	SF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC|SpaceAfter=No
21	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
22	EL	EL	PROPN	M5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC|SpaceAfter=No
23	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
24	KF	KF	PROPN	Z99	Abbr=Yes|Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
25	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	DF	DF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC|SpaceAfter=No
27	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	NB	NB	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC|SpaceAfter=No
29	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
30	FG	FG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
31	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
32	ALT	ALT	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
33	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
34	Bent	Bent	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
35	Bøgsted	Bøgsted	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
36	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
37	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
38	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
39	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
40	Lise	Lise	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
41	Bech	Bech	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
42	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
43	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
44	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
45	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
46	Marie	Marie	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
47	Krarup	Krarup	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
48	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
49	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
50	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
51	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
52	abstention	abstention	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
53	0	0	NUM	Z9	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
54	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.14
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 1.462
# text = Proposal for adoption No V 89 is rejected.
1	Proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
2	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	adoption	adoption	NOUN	A9p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	No	no	DET	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
5	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
6	89	89	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
7	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
8	rejected	reject	VERB	X7n	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
9	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.15
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.483
# text = (Parliament adopted the legislative resolution) V 90 of Peder Hvelplund (EL), and a vote can be taken.
1	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
2	Parliament	Parliament	PROPN	G1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	adopted	adopt	VERB	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
5	legislative	legislative	ADJ	G2.1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
6	resolution	resolution	NOUN	X6p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
9	90	90	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
10	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	Peder	Peder	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
12	Hvelplund	Hvelplund	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
13	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	EL	EL	PROPN	M5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
15	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
16	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
17	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
18	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
19	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
20	can	can	AUX	A7p	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
21	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
22	taken	take	VERB	A9p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
23	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.16
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.751
# text = The vote will end.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	will	will	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	end	end	VERB	T2n	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.17
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 1.543
# text = For the vote 15 (EL, DF, FG and ALT), against 82 (S, V, SF, RV, KF, NB, LA, Bent Bøgsted (UFG), Lise Bech (UFG) and Marie Krarup (UFG), abstention 0.
1	For	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
3	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	15	15	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
5	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	EL	EL	PROPN	M5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	DF	DF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
9	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	FG	FG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
11	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	ALT	ALT	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
13	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
15	against	against	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	82	82	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
17	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
18	S	S	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
20	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
21	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
22	SF	SF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
23	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
24	RV	RV	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
25	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	KF	KF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
27	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	NB	NB	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
29	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
30	LA	LA	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
31	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
32	Bent	Bent	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
33	Bøgsted	Bøgsted	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
34	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
35	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
36	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
37	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
38	Lise	Lise	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
39	Bech	Bech	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
40	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
41	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
42	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
43	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
44	Marie	Marie	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
45	Krarup	Krarup	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
46	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
47	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
48	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
49	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
50	abstention	abstention	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
51	0	0	NUM	Z9	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
52	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.18
# senti_3 = Negative
# senti_6 = mixed negative
# senti_n = 1.401
# text = Proposal for adoption No The V 90 has been rejected.
1	Proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
2	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	adoption	adoption	NOUN	A9p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	No	no	DET	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
5	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
6	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
7	90	90	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
8	has	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
9	been	be	AUX	A3p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
10	rejected	reject	VERB	X7n	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
11	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102117.seg4.19
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.889
# text = That concludes the question.
1	That	that	PRON	Z5	Number=Sing|PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
2	concludes	conclude	VERB	X6p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
4	question	question	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102322
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102322.seg5
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102322.seg5.1
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.972
# text = The debate is closed and we shall proceed to the vote on the motion for a resolution tabled.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	debate	debate	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	closed	close	VERB	A1.1.1	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
5	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	we	we	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Plur|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
7	shall	shall	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
8	proceed	proceed	VERB	A1.1.1	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
9	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
11	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
12	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
14	motion	motion	NOUN	M1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
15	for	for	ADP	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	a	a	DET	T1.3	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
17	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
18	tabled	tab	VERB	Q1.2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102322.seg5.2
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 3.382
# text = There is one proposal.
1	There	there	PRON	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	is	be	VERB	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	one	one	NUM	N1	NumForm=Word|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
4	proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102322.seg5.3
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.365
# text = Motion for a resolution (Doc. V 91 by Kasper Roug (S), Christoffer Aagaard Melson (V), Karsten Hønge (SF), Martin Lidegaard (RV), Christian Juhl (EL), Rasmus Jarlov (KF), Søren Espersen (DF), Peter Seier Christensen (NB), Henrik Dahl (LA), Torsten Gejl (ALT), Aaja Chemnitz Larsen (IA), Aki-Matilda Høegh-Dam-Dam (SIU), Edmund Joensen (SP) and Sjúrður Skaale (JF), and voting is possible.
1	Motion	motion	NOUN	M1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
2	for	for	ADP	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	a	a	DET	T1.3	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
4	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
5	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	Doc.	Doc.	PROPN	T1.3	Abbr=Yes|Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
7	V	V	PROPN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
8	91	91	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
9	by	by	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	Kasper	Kasper	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
11	Roug	Roug	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
12	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
13	S	S	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
15	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	Christoffer	Christoffer	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
17	Aagaard	Aagaard	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
18	Melson	Melson	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
19	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
20	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
21	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
22	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
23	Karsten	Karsten	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
24	Hønge	Hønge	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
25	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
26	SF	SF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
27	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
28	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
29	Martin	Martin	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
30	Lidegaard	Lidegaard	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
31	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
32	RV	RV	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
33	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
34	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
35	Christian	Christian	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
36	Juhl	Juhl	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
37	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
38	EL	EL	PROPN	M5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
39	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
40	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
41	Rasmus	Rasmus	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
42	Jarlov	Jarlov	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
43	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
44	KF	KF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
45	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
46	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
47	Søren	Søren	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
48	Espersen	Espersen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
49	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
50	DF	DF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
51	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
52	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
53	Peter	Peter	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
54	Seier	Seier	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
55	Christensen	Christensen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
56	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
57	NB	NB	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
58	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
59	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
60	Henrik	Henrik	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
61	Dahl	Dahl	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
62	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
63	LA	LA	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
64	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
65	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
66	Torsten	Torsten	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
67	Gejl	Gejl	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
68	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
69	ALT	ALT	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
70	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
71	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
72	Aaja	Aaja	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
73	Chemnitz	Chemnitz	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
74	Larsen	Larsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
75	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
76	IA	IA	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
77	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
78	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
79	Aki-Matilda	Aki-Matilda	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
80	Høegh-Dam	Høegh-Dam	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER|SpaceAfter=No
81	-	-	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
82	Dam	Dam	PROPN	Z3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
83	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
84	SIU	SIU	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
85	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
86	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
87	Edmund	Edmund	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
88	Joensen	Joensen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
89	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
90	SP	SP	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
91	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
92	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
93	Sjúrður	Sjúrður	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
94	Skaale	Skaale	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
95	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
96	JF	JF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
97	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
98	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
99	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
100	voting	voting	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
101	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
102	possible	possible	ADJ	A7p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
103	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102322.seg5.4
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.751
# text = The vote will end.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	vote	vote	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	will	will	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	end	end	VERB	T2n	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102322.seg5.5
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.502
# text = In favour, 96 (S, V, SF, RV, EL, KF, DF, NB, LA, FG, ALT, Bent Bøgsted (UFG), Lise Bech (UFG) and Marie Krarup (UFG)) voted against, 0 abstentions.
1	In	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	favour	favour	NOUN	E2p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
3	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	96	96	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
5	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	S	S	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
9	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	SF	SF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
11	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
12	RV	RV	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
13	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
14	EL	EL	PROPN	M5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
15	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
16	KF	KF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
17	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
18	DF	DF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
20	NB	NB	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
21	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
22	LA	LA	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC|SpaceAfter=No
23	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
24	FG	FG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
25	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
26	ALT	ALT	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
27	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	Bent	Bent	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
29	Bøgsted	Bøgsted	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
30	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
31	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
32	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
33	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
34	Lise	Lise	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
35	Bech	Bech	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
36	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
37	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
38	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
39	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
40	Marie	Marie	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
41	Krarup	Krarup	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
42	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
43	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
44	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
45	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
46	voted	vote	VERB	G1.2	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Past|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
47	against	against	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
48	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
49	0	0	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
50	abstentions	abstention	NOUN	G1.2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
51	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102322.seg5.6
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 3.320
# text = Proposal for adoption No V 91 adopted.
1	Proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
2	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	adoption	adoption	NOUN	A9p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	No	no	DET	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
5	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
6	91	91	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
7	adopted	adopt	VERB	A9p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
8	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102322.seg5.7
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 3.227
# text = That concludes the question.
1	That	that	PRON	Z5	Number=Sing|PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
2	concludes	conclude	VERB	X6p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
4	question	question	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102441
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102441.seg6
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102441.seg6.1
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.533
# text = No amendments have been tabled.
1	No	no	DET	Z6	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	amendments	amendment	NOUN	A2.1p	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
3	have	have	AUX	A9p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	been	be	AUX	A3p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
5	tabled	tab	VERB	Q1.2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602102441.seg6.2
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.672
# text = Does anyone wish to speak?
1	Does	do	AUX	S1.1.3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
2	anyone	anyone	PRON	Z8	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	wish	wish	VERB	X7p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
4	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	speak	speak	VERB	Q2.1	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	?	?	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
