# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130001
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130001.seg1
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130001.seg1.1
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = mixed positive
# senti_n = 3.826
# text = The meeting is open.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	meeting	meeting	NOUN	S1.1.3p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	open	open	ADJ	A10p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130004
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130004.seg2
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130004.seg2.1
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.408
# text = Today there are the following reviews: Minister for Foreign Affairs and Integration (Mattia Tesfaye): Bill no. L 145 (Proposal for a law on temporary residence permits for displaced persons from Ukraine).
1	Today	today	NOUN	T1.1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
2	there	there	PRON	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	are	be	VERB	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
5	following	follow	VERB	M1	VerbForm=Ger	0	_	_	NER=O
6	reviews	review	NOUN	X2.4	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	:	:	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	Minister	Minister	PROPN	G1.1|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
9	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	Foreign	foreign	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
11	Affairs	affair	PROPN	Z1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
12	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
13	Integration	Integration	PROPN	A1.8p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
14	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
15	Mattia	Mattia	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
16	Tesfaye	Tesfaye	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER|SpaceAfter=No
17	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
18	:	:	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
19	Bill	Bill	PROPN	I1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
20	no	no	INTJ	Z4	_	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC|SpaceAfter=No
21	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
22	L	L	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
23	145	145	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=I-MISC
24	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
25	Proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
26	for	for	ADP	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
27	a	a	DET	T1.3	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
28	law	law	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
29	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
30	temporary	temporary	ADJ	T1.3	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
31	residence	residence	NOUN	H1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
32	permits	permit	NOUN	S7.4p	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
33	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
34	displaced	displace	VERB	A2.1p	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
35	persons	person	NOUN	S2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
36	from	from	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
37	Ukraine	Ukraine	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC|SpaceAfter=No
38	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
39	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130004.seg2.2
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.568
# text = Marie Krarup (UFG), Karina Adsbøl (UFG), Lise Bech (UFG), Liselott Blixt (UFG), Bent Bøgsted (UFG) and Hans Kristian Skibby (UFG): Motion for a resolution No. B 188 (Proposal for a Parliament resolution on the extension of local self-government in the field of asylum).
1	Marie	Marie	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
2	Krarup	Krarup	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
3	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
4	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
5	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
6	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
7	Karina	Karina	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
8	Adsbøl	Adsbøl	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
9	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
10	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
11	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
12	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	Lise	Lise	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
14	Bech	Bech	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
15	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
16	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
17	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
18	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
19	Liselott	Liselott	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
20	Blixt	Blixt	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
21	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
22	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
23	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
24	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
25	Bent	Bent	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
26	Bøgsted	Bøgsted	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
27	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
28	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
29	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
30	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
31	Hans	Hans	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
32	Kristian	Kristian	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
33	Skibby	Skibby	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
34	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
35	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
36	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
37	:	:	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
38	Motion	motion	NOUN	M1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
39	for	for	ADP	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
40	a	a	DET	T1.3	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
41	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
42	No.	no.	NOUN	Z99	Abbr=Yes|Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
43	B	b	NUM	Z2	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
44	188	188	NUM	Z2	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
45	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
46	Proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
47	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
48	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
49	Parliament	parliament	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
50	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
51	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
52	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
53	extension	extension	NOUN	H1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
54	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
55	local	local	ADJ	M7	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
56	self	self	NOUN	S5n	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
57	-	-	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
58	government	government	NOUN	G1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
59	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
60	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
61	field	field	NOUN	F4	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
62	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
63	asylum	asylum	NOUN	G1.1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
64	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
65	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130004.seg2.3
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.460
# text = The titles of the notified cases will appear in www.folketingstidende.dk (cf. above).
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	titles	title	NOUN	Q4	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
3	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
5	notified	notify	VERB	Q2.2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
6	cases	case	NOUN	A4.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
7	will	will	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
8	appear	appear	VERB	A8	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
9	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	www.folketingstidende.dk	www.folketingstidende.dk	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
11	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
12	cf.	cf.	NOUN	Z5|A6	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
13	above	above	ADV	M6	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
15	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130035
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130035.seg3
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130035.seg3.1
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.339
# text = There is nothing more to be done in this meeting.
1	There	there	PRON	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	is	be	VERB	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	nothing	nothing	PRON	Z6|Z8	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	more	more	ADJ	A13.3	Degree=Cmp	0	_	_	NER=O
5	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
7	done	do	VERB	A1.1.1	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
8	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
9	this	this	DET	M6	Number=Sing|PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
10	meeting	meeting	NOUN	S1.1.3p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
11	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220314130035.seg3.2
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.603
# text = The next meeting of the Danish Parliament will be held tomorrow, Tuesday, 15 March 2022, at 12.00 p.m. 13.00.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	next	next	ADJ	T1.1.3	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
3	meeting	meeting	NOUN	T1.1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
5	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
6	Danish	Danish	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
7	Parliament	Parliament	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
8	will	will	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
9	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
10	held	hold	VERB	M2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
11	tomorrow	tomorrow	NOUN	T1.1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
12	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	Tuesday	Tuesday	PROPN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
15	15	15	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
16	March	March	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
17	2022	2022	NUM	Z2	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
18	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
19	at	at	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
20	12.00	12.00	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
21	p.m.	p.m.	NOUN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
22	13.00	13.00	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
23	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

