# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080033
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080033.seg1
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080033.seg1.1
# senti_3 = Positive
# senti_6 = mixed positive
# senti_n = 3.826
# text = The meeting is open.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	meeting	meeting	NOUN	S1.1.3p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
3	is	be	AUX	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	open	open	ADJ	A10p	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
5	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080103
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080103.seg2
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080103.seg2.1
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.514
# text = Today there are the following reviews: Leif Lahn Jensen (S), Thomase Danielse (V), Karina Lorentzen Dehnhardt (SF), Andreas Steenberg (RV), Peder Hvelplund (EL), Mai Mercado (KF), Peter Skaarup (DF), Peter Seier Christensen (NB), Ole Birk Olesen (LA), Susanne Zimmer (FG), Torsten Gejl (ALT), Jens Roh (KD), Lars Løkke Rasmussen (M), Aaja Chemnitz Larsen (IA) and Liselott Blixt (UFG): Motion for a resolution No. B 202 (Proposal for a Parliament resolution on free secondary school elections for all (citizens' proposal)).
1	Today	today	NOUN	T1.1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
2	there	there	PRON	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	are	be	VERB	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Plur|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
4	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
5	following	follow	VERB	M1	VerbForm=Ger	0	_	_	NER=O
6	reviews	review	NOUN	X2.4	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
7	:	:	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	Leif	Leif	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
9	Lahn	Lahn	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
10	Jensen	Jensen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
11	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
12	S	S	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
13	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
15	Thomase	Thomase	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
16	Danielse	Danielse	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
17	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
18	V	V	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
19	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
20	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
21	Karina	Karina	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
22	Lorentzen	Lorentzen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
23	Dehnhardt	Dehnhardt	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
24	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
25	SF	SF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
26	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
27	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	Andreas	Andreas	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
29	Steenberg	Steenberg	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
30	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
31	RV	RV	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
32	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
33	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
34	Peder	Peder	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
35	Hvelplund	Hvelplund	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
36	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
37	EL	EL	PROPN	M5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
38	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
39	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
40	Mai	Mai	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
41	Mercado	Mercado	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
42	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
43	KF	KF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
44	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
45	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
46	Peter	Peter	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
47	Skaarup	Skaarup	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
48	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
49	DF	DF	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
50	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
51	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
52	Peter	Peter	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
53	Seier	Seier	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
54	Christensen	Christensen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
55	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
56	NB	NB	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
57	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
58	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
59	Ole	Ole	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
60	Birk	Birk	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
61	Olesen	Olesen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
62	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
63	LA	LA	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
64	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
65	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
66	Susanne	Susanne	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
67	Zimmer	Zimmer	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
68	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
69	FG	FG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
70	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
71	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
72	Torsten	Torsten	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
73	Gejl	Gejl	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
74	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
75	ALT	ALT	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
76	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
77	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
78	Jens	Jens	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
79	Roh	Roh	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
80	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
81	KD	KD	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
82	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
83	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
84	Lars	Lars	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
85	Løkke	Løkke	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
86	Rasmussen	Rasmussen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
87	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
88	M	M	PROPN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
89	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
90	,	,	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
91	Aaja	Aaja	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-PER
92	Chemnitz	Chemnitz	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
93	Larsen	Larsen	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-PER
94	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
95	IA	IA	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
96	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
97	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
98	Liselott	Liselott	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
99	Blixt	Blixt	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
100	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
101	UFG	UFG	PROPN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
102	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
103	:	:	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
104	Motion	motion	NOUN	M1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
105	for	for	ADP	T1.3	_	0	_	_	NER=O
106	a	a	DET	T1.3	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
107	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
108	No.	no.	NOUN	Z99	Abbr=Yes|Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
109	B	b	NUM	Z2	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
110	202	202	NUM	Z2	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
111	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
112	Proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
113	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
114	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
115	Parliament	parliament	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
116	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
117	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
118	free	free	ADJ	S6n	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
119	secondary	secondary	ADJ	P1|H1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
120	school	school	NOUN	P1|H1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
121	elections	election	NOUN	G1.2|X7p	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
122	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
123	all	all	DET	N5.1p	_	0	_	_	NER=O
124	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
125	citizens	citizen	NOUN	G1.1|S2	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
126	'	'	PUNCT	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
127	proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
128	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
129	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
130	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080103.seg2.2
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.775
# text = President. - I call the Group of the European People's Party (Kofod Group). B 203 (Proposal for a Parliament resolution on the ratification by Denmark of the Protocols on the accession of Finland and Sweden to the North Atlantic Treaty).
1	President	President	PROPN	G1.1|S7.1p|S2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
2	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
3	-	-	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	I	I	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Sing|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
5	call	call	VERB	Q2.2	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=1|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
6	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
7	Group	Group	PROPN	S5p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
8	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
9	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
10	European	European	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
11	People	People	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
12	's	's	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
13	Party	Party	PROPN	K1|S1.1.3p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
14	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
15	Kofod	Kofod	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
16	Group	Group	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
17	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
18	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O
19	B	b	NOUN	Z5	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
20	203	203	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
21	(	(	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
22	Proposal	proposal	NOUN	Q2.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
23	for	for	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
24	a	a	DET	Z5	Definite=Ind|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
25	Parliament	parliament	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
26	resolution	resolution	NOUN	T1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
27	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
28	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
29	ratification	ratification	NOUN	S7.4p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
30	by	by	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
31	Denmark	Denmark	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC
32	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
33	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
34	Protocols	Protocols	PROPN	G2.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
35	on	on	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
36	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
37	accession	accession	NOUN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
38	of	of	ADP	Z2	_	0	_	_	NER=O
39	Finland	Finland	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC
40	and	and	CCONJ	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
41	Sweden	Sweden	PROPN	Z2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-LOC
42	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
43	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
44	North	North	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=B-ORG
45	Atlantic	Atlantic	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG
46	Treaty	Treaty	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=I-ORG|SpaceAfter=No
47	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
48	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080103.seg2.3
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.410
# text = The titles of the notified cases will appear in www.folketingstidende.dk. above).
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	titles	title	NOUN	Q4	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
3	of	of	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
5	notified	notify	VERB	Q2.2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
6	cases	case	NOUN	A4.1	Number=Plur	0	_	_	NER=O
7	will	will	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
8	appear	appear	VERB	A8	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
9	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
10	www.folketingstidende.dk.	www.folketingstidende.dk.	X	Z99	_	0	_	_	NER=O
11	above	above	ADV	M6	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
12	)	)	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
13	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# newdoc id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080138
# newpar id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080138.seg3
# lang = en
# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080138.seg3.1
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral negative
# senti_n = 2.339
# text = There is nothing more to be done in this meeting.
1	There	there	PRON	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
2	is	be	VERB	A3p	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=3|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	nothing	nothing	PRON	Z6|Z8	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	more	more	ADJ	A13.3	Degree=Cmp	0	_	_	NER=O
5	to	to	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
6	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
7	done	do	VERB	A1.1.1	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
8	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
9	this	this	DET	M6	Number=Sing|PronType=Dem	0	_	_	NER=O
10	meeting	meeting	NOUN	S1.1.3p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
11	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080138.seg3.2
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.659
# text = The next meeting will be held today at 2 p.m. 8.20.
1	The	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
2	next	next	ADJ	T1.1.3	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=O
3	meeting	meeting	NOUN	T1.1.3	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
4	will	will	AUX	T1.1.3	VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
5	be	be	AUX	A3p	VerbForm=Inf	0	_	_	NER=O
6	held	hold	VERB	M2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part|Voice=Pass	0	_	_	NER=O
7	today	today	NOUN	T1.1.2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
8	at	at	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
9	2	2	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O
10	p.m.	p.m.	NOUN	Z99	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
11	8.20	8.20	NUM	N1	NumForm=Digit|NumType=Card	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
12	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

# sent_id = ParlaMint-DK_20220602080138.seg3.3
# senti_3 = Neutral
# senti_6 = neutral positive
# senti_n = 2.825
# text = I refer to the agenda set out in the Danish Parliament's website.
1	I	I	PRON	Z8	Case=Nom|Number=Sing|Person=1|PronType=Prs	0	_	_	NER=O
2	refer	refer	VERB	Q2.2	Mood=Ind|Number=Sing|Person=1|Tense=Pres|VerbForm=Fin	0	_	_	NER=O
3	to	to	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
4	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
5	agenda	agenda	NOUN	Q1.2|X7p	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O
6	set	set	VERB	M2	Tense=Past|VerbForm=Part	0	_	_	NER=O
7	out	out	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
8	in	in	ADP	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
9	the	the	DET	Z5	Definite=Def|PronType=Art	0	_	_	NER=O
10	Danish	Danish	ADJ	Z1	Degree=Pos	0	_	_	NER=B-MISC
11	Parliament	Parliament	PROPN	Z1	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
12	's	's	PART	Z5	_	0	_	_	NER=O
13	website	website	NOUN	Y2	Number=Sing	0	_	_	NER=O|SpaceAfter=No
14	.	.	PUNCT	Z9	_	0	_	_	NER=O

